[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The script for Spaceballs, a Mel Brooks parody of the Star Wars and Star Trek franchises, was approved by George Lucas.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which Academy Award-winning actress voiced the dragon in the film Eragon?", "correct_answer": "Rachel Weisz", "incorrect_answers": ["Gweneth Paltrow", "Julia Roberts", "Dame Judi Dench"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year did the dodo become extinct?", "correct_answer": "1681", "incorrect_answers": ["1705", "1789", "1803"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the symbol for Bismuth?", "correct_answer": "Bi", "incorrect_answers": ["Bs", "B", "Bm"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Women blink more often than men.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Vitamin C and Vitamins of the B group are crucial for the proper functioning of the body.  Are they considered to be complex, fat-soluble substances?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Fast Times at Ridgemont High, directed by Amy Heckerling, was released to theaters in what year?", "correct_answer": "1982", "incorrect_answers": ["1989", "1972", "1992"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1916 young Antonio Gentile won a $5 prize for an original drawing. The drawing eventually became this.", "correct_answer": "Mr. Peanut", "incorrect_answers": ["The model for Picassos Lady With Guitar", "The model for Paramount Studios logo", "The Coca Cola bottle"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Sun has how many times the diameter of the Earth?", "correct_answer": "110", "incorrect_answers": ["150", "100", "135"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these expression does not refer to a yolkless egg?", "correct_answer": "Vain egg", "incorrect_answers": ["Wind egg", "Dwarf egg", "Cock egg"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What islands are knows as \u201cThe beautiful garland in the Indian Ocean\u201d?", "correct_answer": "Maldives Islands", "incorrect_answers": ["Aeolian Islands", "Pontine Islands", "Flegrean Islands"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are baby teeth scientifically called?", "correct_answer": "Deciduous teeth", "incorrect_answers": ["Toddler teeth", "Begginers teeth", "Osseous Tissue"]}]